<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>If you could have any superpower, would you choose the ability to talk to squirrels or turn invisible when no one’s looking?</item>
        <item>What’s the weirdest food combination you secretly love?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet dragon or a pet unicorn?</item>
        <item>If your pet could talk, what do you think it would say about you?</item>
        <item>What’s your go-to dance move when nobody’s watching?</item>
        <item>If you could swap lives with a cartoon character for a day, who would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the silliest thing you’ve ever done for a dare?</item>
        <item>If you could only eat one type of candy for the rest of your life, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up one morning with purple hair and couldn’t change it?</item>
        <item>If you could create a holiday, what would it be called and how would you celebrate it?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have fingers for toes or toes for fingers?</item>
        <item>If you could be any animal for a day, which one would you choose and why?</item>
        <item>What’s the most embarrassing thing that’s ever happened to you in school?</item>
        <item>If you could have a lifetime supply of any snack, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the weirdest dream you’ve ever had?</item>
        <item>If you could travel back in time and meet any historical figure, who would it be and what would you ask them?</item>
        <item>Would you rather always have to hop on one foot or skip everywhere you go?</item>
        <item>If you could only wear one color for the rest of your life, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you found a talking potato in your fridge?</item>
        <item>If you could make one rule that everyone in the world had to follow, what would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a never-ending supply of pizza or ice cream?</item>
        <item>If you were a superhero, what would your catchphrase be when you saved the day?</item>
        <item>What’s the most bizarre thing you’ve ever seen a seagull do?</item>
        <item>If you could make any animal the size of a house, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up one morning and gravity was reversed?</item>
        <item>If you had to eat a whole jar of peanut butter in one sitting, would you choose smooth or crunchy?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous fashion trend you’ve ever tried?</item>
        <item>If you could turn any movie into a musical, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the funniest joke you know by heart?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have to sing everything you say or dance every time you walk?</item>
        <item>If you could have a conversation with your pet, what’s the first thing you’d ask them?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could hear everyone’s thoughts for a day?</item>
        <item>If you could make a potion that turns people into animals, what animal would you choose for your worst enemy?</item>
        <item>What’s the strangest smell you’ve ever encountered?</item>
        <item>If you could visit any planet in our solar system, which one would you go to?</item>
        <item>What’s your go-to karaoke song when you’re feeling extra silly?</item>
        <item>If you had a magic wand, what’s the first thing you’d use it for?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet dinosaur or a pet alien from outer space?</item>
        <item>If you could live inside a video game, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous food challenge you’d be willing to attempt?</item>
        <item>If you could have a lifetime supply of any beverage, what would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a talking pet hamster or a flying pet goldfish?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up with a unicorn horn on your forehead?</item>
        <item>If you could have any job in the world for a day, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the most unusual talent you possess?</item>
        <item>If you could make it rain anything besides water, what would you choose?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet penguin or a pet kangaroo?</item>
        <item>What’s the most bizarre thing you’ve ever found in your backpack?</item>
        <item>If you could have any animal as a sidekick, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the weirdest thing you’ve ever seen in a cloud formation?</item>
        <item>If you could swap places with a famous person for a day, who would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have spaghetti for hair or marshmallows for teeth?</item>
        <item>What’s the silliest thing you’ve ever done with a balloon?</item>
        <item>If you could turn any book into a real-life adventure, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could control the weather for a day?</item>
        <item>If you had to survive in the wilderness, what three items would you take with you?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet dinosaur that fits in your pocket or a pet elephant that can fly?</item>
        <item>What’s the most absurd thing you’ve ever tried to teach your pet?</item>
        <item>If you could make one animal the ruler of the world, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up with a tail like a monkey?</item>
        <item>If you could turn any food into a musical instrument, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What’s the funniest animal noise you can make?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a lifetime supply of bubblegum or confetti?</item>
        <item>If you could communicate with one type of insect, which one would you choose?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you discovered a secret portal to a different dimension in your closet?</item>
        <item>If you could have a conversation with a plant, what plant would you choose?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal chef who only cooks pancakes or a personal DJ who only plays polka music?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous thing you’ve ever tried to juggle?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet rock that granted wishes, what would you name it?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could turn into a giant rubber duck for a day?</item>
        <item>If you could have a robot that did one silly task for you, what would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a talking stuffed animal or a singing refrigerator?</item>
        <item>What’s the craziest adventure you’ve ever imagined while looking at clouds?</item>
        <item>If you could make any food float in the air, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if your favorite cartoon character showed up at your front door?</item>
        <item>If you could have a parade in your honor, what would it be called?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet monkey that can talk or a pet sloth that can dance?</item>
        <item>What’s the most outrageous hairstyle you’ve ever wanted to try?</item>
        <item>If you could turn any vegetable into a superhero, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make your bed teleport to any location?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet cloud that rained your favorite drink, what would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a closet full of costumes or a secret hideout in your backyard?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous way you’ve ever tried to impress someone?</item>
        <item>If you could have a theme song that played whenever you entered a room, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you discovered a treasure map in a bottle on the beach?</item>
        <item>If you could have a talking pillow, what would you ask it?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet octopus with a top hat or a pet giraffe on roller skates?</item>
        <item>What’s the most hilarious sound effect you can mimic?</item>
        <item>If you could make any vegetable dance, which one would you choose?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up in a world made entirely of candy?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic pen that brought your drawings to life, what would you draw first?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal cloud that follows you everywhere or a talking toaster that tells jokes?</item>
        <item>What’s the goofiest face you can make on command?</item>
        <item>If you could make it snow something other than snowflakes, what would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you discovered a secret tunnel in your backyard?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet dragon that breathed bubbles instead of fire, what color would the bubbles be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a closet full of shoes that make you jump super high or hats that give you crazy hairstyles?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous way you’ve ever tried to travel from one room to another?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic backpack that produced any snack you wanted, what snack would it make first?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make your voice sound like any animal?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet robot that does your homework, what would you name it?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal theme song that plays whenever you talk or a personal cloud that shades you from the sun?</item>
        <item>What’s the silliest thing you’ve ever drawn on the sidewalk with chalk?</item>
        <item>If you could have a conversation with a talking tree, what kind of tree would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you found a treasure chest filled with rubber ducks?</item>
        <item>If you could make it rain any type of candy, what would you choose?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet penguin that can tap dance or a pet kangaroo that tells jokes?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous way you’ve ever tried to wake someone up?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet cloud that turns into any shape you want, what shape would it be right now?</item>
        <item>If you could make any food sing a song, what food would you choose?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make your voice sound like a robot for a day?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal robot that does your chores or a personal unicorn that gives you rides to school?</item>
        <item>What’s the most bizarre thing you’ve ever found in your lunchbox?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet dragon that only breathes bubbles, what flavor would the bubbles be?</item>
        <item>If you could make any vegetable talk, which one would it be?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you discovered a hidden room in your house filled with candy?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic remote control that paused time, what’s the first thing you’d do?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet sloth that can do magic tricks or a pet flamingo that can sing opera?</item>
        <item>What’s the craziest way you’ve ever tried to make someone laugh?</item>
        <item>If you could have a personal cloud that follows you and plays your favorite music, what song would it play right now?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make it snow confetti instead of snowflakes?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet robot that told you jokes all day, what would you name it?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a talking backpack or a flying skateboard?</item>
        <item>What’s the most outrageous hat you’ve ever worn?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic wand that turned anything into candy, what would you wave it at first?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could turn any vegetable into a superhero costume?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet dragon that could only say one word, what word would it be?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal theme song that plays every time you jump or a talking umbrella that gives you compliments?</item>
        <item>What’s the goofiest dance move you can come up with?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic pen that drew invisible pictures, what would you draw?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make your voice sound like a chipmunk for a day?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal cloud that rains confetti or a pet unicorn that farts glitter?</item>
        <item>What’s the most ridiculous way you’ve ever tried to start a conversation with someone?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet robot that danced to your favorite song, what song would it dance to?</item>
        <item>If you could have a talking tree as a friend, what would you name it?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you found a treasure chest filled with rubber chickens?</item>
        <item>If you could make it rain any type of fruit, what fruit would you choose?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet penguin that wears sunglasses or a pet kangaroo that can do backflips?</item>
        <item>What’s the craziest way you’ve ever tried to solve a problem?</item>
        <item>If you could have a personal cloud that gave you shade on hot days, what shape would it be right now?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could make your voice sound like a robot monkey for a day?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a pet robot that can bake cookies or a pet unicorn that can grant wishes?</item>
        <item>What’s the most outrageous thing you’ve ever tried to fit in your backpack?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic remote control that made any food appear in front of you, what food would you choose?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you could turn any vegetable into a talking puppet?</item>
        <item>If you could have a pet dragon that only knows how to do the moonwalk, would you teach it any other dance moves?</item>
        <item>Would you rather have a personal theme song that plays whenever you sneeze or a talking umbrella that tells jokes?</item>
        <item>What’s the funniest face you can make on command?</item>
        <item>If you could have a magic pen that made your drawings come to life as miniature versions of themselves, what would you draw first?</item>
        <item>What would you do if you woke up one day and all the colors in the world were swapped?</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
